adidas.ie 2019-12-11

# Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY NOTICE**

valid as of 2 October 2019

******1.** **      ****What does this Privacy Notice tell you?** ****

**2.** **      ****Who are the adidas Data Controllers?** ****

**3.** **      ****How do you get in touch with the Data Protection Officer of the adidas Data Controllers?** ****

**4.** **      ****What Personal Data does adidas collect and use (Categories of Personal Data)?** ****

**5.** **      ****What does adidas do with your Personal Data and why (Purpose,   Processing, Legal Basis)?** ****

I.     SITE (ADIDAS DOMAIN) OPERATION AND APP OPERATION

II.    DOMAIN AND NETWORK SECURITY AND USER AUTHENTICATION

III.   GLOBAL CREDENTIAL TO ALL ADIDAS PLATFORMS – USER EXPERIENCE

IV.   SALES OF ADIDAS PRODUCTS - ONLINE AND OFF-LINE ORDER

V.    PAYMENT FRAUD DETECTION

VI.   PRODUCT DELIVERY

VII.  ELECTRONIC DELIVERY TRACKING

VIII. BUSINESS OPERATIONAL ANALYTICS

IX.    CUSTOMER SERVICE

X.    PERSONALISED MARKETING MESSAGES VIA EMAIL (Newsletter Sign-Up)

XI.   PERSONALISED MARKETING MESSAGES VIA EMAIL (via existing contract)

XII.  TARGETED MESSAGES ON 3RD-PARTY ADVERTISING PLATFORMS

XIII.    CREATORS CLUB MEMBERSHIP ADMINISTRATION – WHERE APPLICABLE

XIV.    PRIVATE EVENT REGISTRATION

XV.     OPEN EVENT REGISTRATION

XVI.    PRODUCT RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT

XVII.    LEGAL OBLIGATION - COOPERATION WITH LAW ENFORCEMENT AND REGULATORY AUTHORITIES (INCLUDING COURTS)

XVIII.   COLLECTING YOUR DEVICE INFORMATION ON OUR WEBSITE USING COOKIES, PIXELS, TAGS, AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES (“COOKIES NOTICE”)

XIX.    USER-GENERATED CONTENT (UGC) ACQUISITION FROM SOCIAL MEDIA

XX.     PUSH NOTIFICATIONS (IN-APP COMMUNICATION)

**6.** **      ****What does adidas do when we transfer your Personal Data outside of the EU/EEA?** ****

**7.** **      ****How do we secure your Personal Data?** ****

**8.** **      ****What are your rights and how can you exercise them?** ****

**9.** **      ****Questions, Complaints, and Support – who and how you can get in touch with them?** ****

**10.** **       ****Updates and Notification of Updates** ****

**11.** **       ****adidas Data Recipients** ****

  1. What does this Privacy Notice tell you?

This Privacy Notice tells you how we collect and process the information from which you can be identified directly or indirectly (“ **Personal Data** ”) while you browse <https://www.adidas.ie/> as well as when you interact with different adidas platforms, portals and applications using your Personal Data (“ **adidas platforms** ”). 

This Privacy Notice provides information on: 

**a)** adidas Data Controllers; 

**b)** Data Protection Officer; 

**c)** the different types of Personal Data we use (“ **Categories of Personal Data”)** ; 

**d)** why and how we use your Personal Data (“ **Purpose** ”; “ **Processing”** ; “ **Lawful basis”** ); 

**e)** how long your Personal Data is kept (“ **Retention period** ”); 

**f)** other recipients of your Personal Data (“ **Recipients** ”); 

**g)** transferring your Personal Data out of the EU/EEA (“ **International Data Transfer** ”); 

**h)** your rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation and national applicable laws; and 

**i)** any automated decision-making technologies used by us and how it works (where necessary). 

  2. Who are the adidas Data Controllers?

The following adidas Data Controllers jointly determine how your Personal Data is used by adidas for the purposes identified in the adidas Privacy Notice (“Joint Controllers”). They are responsible for protecting your Personal Data and complying with GDPR and national legislation governing the use of your Personal Data.

  * **adidas AG** \- Adi-Dassler Str. 1, 91074 Herzogenaurach, Germany **(”adidas AG”)**
  * **adidas Business Services GmbH** \- Adi-Dassler Str. 1, 91074 Herzogenaurach, Germany
  * **adidas (Ireland) Limited** \- Nangor Road, Nangor Road Business Park Unit C1, Clondalkin, Dublin 12, Ireland **(“Local Selling Entity”)**

For the purposes of

  * **Sales of adidas products – online and off-line order**
  * **Product research and development**

the legal entities identified below form Joint Controllers:

  * **adidas AG**
  * **adidas International Trading AG** \- Am Platz 10, 6039 Root D4, Switzerland
  * **Local Selling Entity** ****

  3. How do you get in touch with the Data Protection Officer of the adidas Data Controllers?

**Global Privacy | Data Protection Officer**

**adidas AG**

Adi-Dassler-Straße 1

91074 Herzogenaurach

Germany

  4. What Personal Data does adidas collect and use (Categories of Personal Data)?

These are the categories of Personal Data we collect directly or indirectly from you: 

  * **Identity information** – includes: name [first, last, initials], Date of Birth, e-mail address, unique consumer identifier number (including your Creators Club member ID), nickname, password, social media identifiers and information passed along to us via your Facebook or Runtastic account, your device fingerprint, and gift card codes that are assigned to you. We use it to verify your identity. 

---  
  
  * **Contact information** \- includes: your phone number, shipping and billing address, e-mail address, Messenger ID, social media handle, any other communication channel you have used to contact us for more information. We use it to contact you for different reasons depending on the purposes stated below. ****

  * **Location information** - **** includes: your residential location, current log-in location [IP address], GPS location (if you wish to share us, for example through your mobile device settings), or the specific adidas site you have visited that might give us clues about where you are. We use it to help you find what you are looking for at your current location. ****

  * **Size information** \- includes: shoe size, clothes size, height, weight, chest, waist, hip, inseam, body shape, heel-toe measurement. We use it to make sure your gear fits. ****

  * **Purchase information** - **** includes: your payment information (credit card number), payment risk profile (provided to us by our payment risk solution), shopping cart (your ordered items), delivery details, shipping and billing address, customer order number, purchase history with adidas, transaction ID, and any other information related to your purchase. We use it to complete your order on adidas sites and apps, in adidas stores, or other selling platforms. ****

  * **Behavioural and Profile information** \- includes: your shopping history, Wishlist items, your browsing behaviour, your browsing preferences, your shopping preferences, in-store interactions, your workout history, product reviews, social media interactions with us, and any other intelligence we have about you to help us learn you as a consumer better, including “Community information”. We use it to know you better as a consumer, so we can send you marketing messages containing only products and services that we think you might be interested in. ****

  * **Community information** – includes: information provided by you when you participate various adidas events and communities either as a trainer, team member, a participant or as a promotor of our events, including for example: pictures, videos, your nickname, your team, your interests and preferences, your feedback, leader boards, event participation, joined groups, and registration details. We use this information to organise the events and communities, and to know more about you as a consumer. ****

  * **Social Media information** – includes: information obtained through your interaction with us on various social media channels such as Facebook, Instagram, Google, etc., including: any social media information that is publicly available such as your social media handles, social media interactions and public postings, your “Likes” and other reactions, your social media connections, your photos that are public, or those you send to us by mentioning us or following our social media posts by using “handles” or “hashtags”. We obtain this information from the social media network (e.g. Facebook, Snapchat, Instagram, etc.) directly or indirectly through third-party agencies we have agreements with. ****

  * **Device information** – includes: Information about your device or browser that give us an idea about your browsing behaviour or device usage. Your device information is collected by our app, and your browser information is collected by our cookies, tags, and pixels. This is often required for network security purposes. This includes, but not limited to: IP address, date and time of the visit, how long you remained on our website, the referral URL (if you came to our site via a different site or an advertisement), the pages visited on our site, your browser type, device type, versions, operating system. ****

  * **Activity information** \- includes: fitness data (for example workout start and end times, activity type, sports category), sensor data (for example step goal, duration, pace, distance, calories, heartbeat, RunScore and speed), and other data related to your fitness app. We use it to help you improve your performance goals and improve your user experiences and identify what products might be best for you based on your exercise patterns. ****

  * **Correspondence** – includes: conversation we have when you contact customer service, the emails you write us about our products or services, the complaints you address to us via post, e-mail, fax, or call, notes we prepared on your feedback, call back from our Customer Service to you, and any other communication between you and adidas personnel. We record all Customer Service calls for quality assurance purposes. ****

  * **Preference information** \- includes: preferred language, log-in location, Wishlist items, preferred shipping address, browsing preferences, our correspondence with you, your adidas product reviews. We use it to give you convenience when you visit and/or shop on our sites and apps. ****

  * **Creators Club information** – includes: Unique Member Identifier (member ID), date you became a member, store ID (if you signed up in a retail store), source ID, country and brand of your original membership, membership points, engagement history, rewards history, membership vouchers associated to members. All the information the listed here will be kept for as long as you are a Creators Club member.   ****

  5. What does adidas do with your Personal Data and why (Purpose,  Processing, Legal Basis)?

**Purpose**

| 

**Legal Basis**  
  
---|---  
  
  * I. Site (Adidas Domain) Operation and App Operation

| 

Legitimate Interest  
  
  * II. Domain and Network Security and User Authentication

| 

Legitimate Interest  
  
  * III. Global Credential to All Adidas Platforms – User Experience

| 

Legitimate Interest  
  
  * IV. Sales of adidas Products - Online and Off-Line Order

| 

Performance of Contract  
  
  * V. Payment Fraud Detection

| 

Performance of Contract  
  
  * VI. Product Delivery

| 

Performance of Contract  
  
  * VII. Electronic Delivery Tracking

| 

Consent  
  
  * VIII. Business Operational Analytics

| 

Legitimate Interest  
  
  * IX. Customer Service

| 

Legitimate Interest  
  
  * X. Personalised Marketing Messages Via Email (Newsletter Sign-Up)

| 

Consent  
  
  * XI. Personalised Marketing Messages Via Email (Via Existing Contract)

| 

Legitimate interest  
  
  * XII. Targeted Messages On 3rd-Party Advertising Platforms

| 

Consent  
  
  * XIII. Creators Club Membership Administration – Where Applicable

| 

Performance of Contract  
  
  * XIV. Private Event Registration

| 

Performance of Contract  
  
  * XV. Open Event Registration

| 

Legitimate Interest  
  
  * XVI. Product Research and Development

| 

Legitimate interest  
  
  17. Legal Obligation - Cooperation with Law Enforcement And Regulatory Authorities (Including Courts)

| 

Legal Obligation  
  
  18. Collecting Your Device Information on Our Website Using Cookies, Pixels, Tags, And Similar Technologies (“Cookies Notice”)

| 

Legitimate Interest | Consent  
  
  * XIX. User-Generated Content (UGC) Acquisition From Social Media

| 

Performance of Contract  
  
  * XX. Push Notifications (In-App Communication)

| 

Legitimate Interest  
  
  |   |    
  
In this section, we explain: 

  1. When and Why do we need your Personal Data (“ **Purpose** ”)?
  2. What allows us to use your Personal Data for each Purpose (“ **Legal basis** ”)? 
  3. What do we do to your Personal Data for each Purpose (“ **Processing** ”)?
  4. Which of your Personal Data do we need for each Purpose (“ **Categories of Personal Data** ”)?
  5. How long do we keep your Personal Data for each Purpose (“ **Retention period** ”)?
  6. With whom (types of service providers) do we share your Personal Data to achieve the purpose (“ **Categories of recipients** ”)?

  * I. SITE (ADIDAS DOMAIN) OPERATION AND APP OPERATION

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

To run the sites that are connected to the adidas domain and the adidas app, fix bugs to make sure you always see the site the way we intended, and monitor compliance with our Terms and Conditions, we screen all traffic to our site and analyse data that is received by our servers. 

**Use of Cookies/Tags/Pixels:** We may collect your personal details for this purpose by using technologies such as cookies, pixels and tags to collect your device information. More information is available in “ **XVIII.     COLLECTING YOUR DEVICE INFORMATION ON OUR WEBSITE USING COOKIES, PIXELS, TAGS, AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES**”.  
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Legitimate Interest  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Device information

Identity information

Behavioural and Profile information 

Preference information  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

**Browsing Session**

We need your data for as long as you are on the site. We keep it for the duration of your browsing session.   
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates 
  * Site Administration Support Providers

  * II. DOMAIN AND NETWORK SECURITY AND USER AUTHENTICATION

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

To protect our domains, detect unusual activities, and prevent security threats and protect our site-visitors from unauthorised accesses (such as hackers), we screen all traffic to our sites, and authenticate user log-in information using tokens to verify the details you provide to us and compare it with other available information, such us the credentials you have provided directly to adidas or other platforms (such as Runtastic or Facebook) or information that is available in the public domain to ensure only “authorised” users have access to our sites. 

**Use of Cookies/Tags/Pixels:** We may collect your personal details for this purpose by using technologies such as cookies, pixels and tags to collect your device information. More information is available in “ **XVIII.      COLLECTING YOUR DEVICE INFORMATION ON OUR WEBSITE USING COOKIES, PIXELS, TAGS, AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES**”.  
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Legitimate Interest  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Device information

Identity information

Behavioural and Profile information 

Preference information  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

**Browsing Session**

We need your data for as long as you are on the site. We keep it for the duration of your browsing session.  
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates 
  * Site Administration Support Providers

  * III. GLOBAL CREDENTIAL TO ALL ADIDAS PLATFORMS – USER EXPERIENCE

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

We know you don’t like to remember usernames and passwords, or having to register multiple times. 

To enable our users to log on to all platforms, portals, services, communities and apps operated by or on behalf of adidas Data Controllers (which includes the Runtastic app and services) (“ **adidas Platforms** ”) with one set of log-in credentials (“adidas Log-In”), we store your adidas Log-In in our global authentication platform. When you use your adidas Log-In to enter any adidas Platform, we will use a token to verify your identity from our global authentication platform. This also further ensures our network and domain security.

**Use of Cookies/Tags/Pixels:** We may collect your personal details for this purpose by using technologies such as cookies, pixels and tags to collect your device information. More information is available in “ **XVIII.      COLLECTING YOUR DEVICE INFORMATION ON OUR WEBSITE USING COOKIES, PIXELS, TAGS, AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES**”.  
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Legitimate Interest  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Identity information 

Creators Club information (for Creators Club members only)

Preference information  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

**Your account duration or Inactivity+25 months**

To allow you to sign in with your adidas Log-In on adidas Platforms, we need to maintain your data for as long as you have an account with us, or if you stop using our services without requesting to delete your data, we will keep it for 25 months after your last log in.  
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates 
  * Site Administration Support Providers

  * IV. SALES OF ADIDAS PRODUCTS - ONLINE AND OFF-LINE ORDER

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

To process your online and/or in-app orders, make sure your payment is received, comply with the requirements under our Terms and Conditions (3. Purchase Terms) (for selling you the products) including invoice processing, delivery, personalisation services, exchanges and refunds, click and collect. Your order cannot be completed if our payment fraud detection solutions flag your transaction as suspicious and potentially fraudulent.  Please note the payment fraud detection system is an automated decision-making process. It is required to allow us to conclude the contract with you. You have the right to request a human review of this decision, and challenge the decision.   
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Performance of Contract  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Identity information

Contact information

Location information

Size information

Purchase information

Correspondence

Device information

Creators Club information (for Creators Club members only)  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

Duration of contract and statutory limitation period. We need to keep the information in case of any legal disputes concerning the contract.   
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates 
  * Selling Partners (where applicable)
  * Manufacturing Providers
  * Delivery Service Providers
  * Payment Risk Solution Providers
  * Payment Processing Providers
  * IT Cloud Solution Providers

  * V. PAYMENT FRAUD DETECTION

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

We combine the purchase information you provide to us with other information we obtain through our third-party payment risk and fraud prevention service providers to ensure any purchases are legitimate, or you do not purchase our products in violation with our terms and conditions. This means depending on the outcome of the analysis of your information, we may reject your order, and decline your payment. This is an automated decision-making process that is required to conclude our sales contract with you.  
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Performance of Contract  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Identity information

Contact information

Behavioural and Profile information 

Purchase information

Device information  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

Duration of contract and statutory limitation period. We need to keep the information in case of any legal disputes concerning the contract.   
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates 
  * Payment Risk Solution Providers
  * Payment Processing Providers
  * IT Cloud Solution Providers

  * VI. PRODUCT DELIVERY

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

Once you have successfully placed an order, we use your contact details (home and/or shipping address) and other purchase information to deliver the products you purchased to you.  
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Performance of Contract  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Identity information: Name

Contact information: Shipping Address  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

Duration of contract and statutory limitation period. We need to keep the information in case of any legal disputes concerning the contract.   
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates 
  * Delivery Service Providers
  * IT Cloud Solution Providers

  * VII. ELECTRONIC DELIVERY TRACKING

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

**_This is a service provided on request of the consumer by our Delivery Partners._**

You have the option to track your delivery using services provided directly by our delivery partners; however, we will only be able to share your information with our delivery partners for this purpose with your consent. The service is hosted on the Delivery Partner’s platform. You should read their Privacy Notice for the processing of your Personal Data for this purpose.  
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Consent  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Identity information

Contact information

Any other information you may directly and voluntarily provide to the Delivery Partner  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

As determined by our Delivery Partner.   
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * Delivery Service Providers

  8. BUSINESS OPERATIONAL ANALYTICS

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

We need to know how we do as a business. This is in the interest of our shareholders, our board members, our employees, and our partners. For this purpose, we need to analyse different categories of information to understand how our products are selling in different markets, what are the popular features of our products, what worked and what didn’t in terms of our marketing and advertising campaigns, our product designs and distribution strategy, our website design and overall user experience, so we can establish, implement, and evaluate our business strategy. 

This includes analysing data to understand how users browse our site and use the app to improve our user experience design to make sure you will continue to purchase our products and interact with us on our sites and applications. 

To minimise the risk to you as an individual, we will only use either the unique consumer identifier or the IP address for this purpose. 

You can learn more about how our Data Analytics Solution Providers provide analytics services by using your data here:

Adobe Analytics Data Collection: <https://marketing.adobe.com/resources/help/en_US/reference/c_Privacy_Overview.html>

Google Analytics Data Collection:

<https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6318039?hl=en>  
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Legitimate Interest  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Identity information: Unique Consumer Identifier (only)

Size information 

Purchase information

Behavioural and Profile information 

Community information

Activity information

Device information

Correspondence

Creators Club information (for Creators Club members only)  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

When using analytics services provided by the vendors identified above, we are required to retain data for the period specified by these vendors. You can find the retention period indicated by the vendors here:

Adobe Analytics: 36 months (<https://marketing.adobe.com/resources/help/en_US/reference/data-retention.html> )

Google Analytics: 38 months

(<https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/7667196?hl=en>)

We need the information for this duration to produce accurate analysis of our business operations.   
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates 
  * Prospective Buyers and Investors
  * Business Consulting Service Providers
  * Data Analytics Solution Providers
  * IT Cloud Solution Providers

  * IX. CUSTOMER SERVICE

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

We collect your Personal Data to tell you when the product you like is available upon your request and respond to your questions and concerns through various communications channels we make available to you.  
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Legitimate Interest  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Identity information

Contact information

Location information

Size information

Purchase information

Correspondence

Creators Club information (for Creators Club members only)  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

Statutory limitation period. We need to keep the information in case of any legal disputes.  
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * Customer Service Provider
  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates 
  * Selling Partners (where applicable)
  * Delivery Service Providers
  * Payment Risk Solution Providers
  * Payment Processing Providers
  * IT Cloud Solution Providers

  * X. PERSONALISED MARKETING MESSAGES VIA EMAIL (Newsletter Sign-Up)

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

We send you marketing messages that we think you would be interested (“personalised”) to the email address you provide to us because you signed up to our email newsletters. To send you “personalised” messages, we observe your online (and sometimes, where applicable, offline) behaviour, and analyse your behaviour using analytics to best estimate what product lines you might be interested in, and you can benefit from. This requires us to collect various categories of Personal Data from you. We use different analytics tools to understand what your behaviour means in terms of your like and dislike of our various product lines, and to understand the impact (success rates) of the messages delivered to you.

**Use of Cookies/Tags/Pixels:** We may collect your personal details for this purpose by using technologies such as cookies, pixels and tags to collect your device information. More information is available in “ **XVIII.             COLLECTING YOUR DEVICE INFORMATION ON OUR WEBSITE USING COOKIES, PIXELS, TAGS, AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES**”.   
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Consent  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Identity information

Contact information (if available to adidas)

Location information

Size information (if available to adidas)

Purchase information (if available to adidas)

Behavioural and Profile information (if available to adidas)

Community information (if available to adidas)

Social Media information (if available to adidas)

Activity information (if available to adidas)

Device information

Preference information (if available to adidas)  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

We retain it for as long as you do not withdraw your consent sending you emails or object to us processing your Personal Data for marketing purposes.  
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates 
  * Email Marketing Support Providers
  * IT Cloud Solution Providers

| 

  * XI. PERSONALISED MARKETING MESSAGES VIA EMAIL (via existing contract)

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

We send you marketing messages that we think you would be interested in (“personalised”) to the email address you provide to us during a purchasing contract. To send you “personalised” messages, we observe your online (and sometimes, where applicable, offline) behaviour, and analyse your behaviour using analytics to best estimate what product lines you might be interested in, and you can benefit from. This requires us to collect various categories of Personal Data from you. We use different analytics tools to understand what your behaviour means in terms of your like and dislike of our various product lines, and to understand the impact (success rates) of the messages delivered to you.

**Use of Cookies/Tags/Pixels:** We may collect your personal details for this purpose by using technologies such as cookies, pixels and tags to collect your device information. More information is available in “ **XVIII.      COLLECTING YOUR DEVICE INFORMATION ON OUR WEBSITE USING COOKIES, PIXELS, TAGS, AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES**”.   
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Legitimate interest  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Identity information

Contact information (if available to adidas)

Location information

Size information (if available to adidas)

Purchase information (if available to adidas)

Behavioural and Profile information (if available to adidas)

Community information (if available to adidas)

Social Media information (if available to adidas)

Activity information (if available to adidas)

Device information

Preference information (if available to adidas)

Creators Club information (for Creators Club members only)  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

We retain it for as long as you do not object to us processing your Personal Data for marketing purposes, including sending of marketing messages.  
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates 
  * Email Marketing Support Providers
  * IT Cloud Solution Providers

| 

  * XII. TARGETED MESSAGES ON 3RD-PARTY ADVERTISING PLATFORMS

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

We use third-party advertising platforms, such as Facebook, Google, YouTube, Instagram, etc. to send you messages that are targeted at you, based on your behaviour and browsing pattern, at specific times and locations of these platforms to increase the efficiency of our advertising campaigns. We use third-party solutions such as **Google Audience** and **Facebook Custom Audience** to help us do a better job at targeting our campaigns and messages for our consumers. Your Personal Data is shared with the third-party advertising platforms, and they will attempt to match your profile in their database to determine the optimal time and place (the page you are browsing) to show you an advertisement from adidas. We also need to analyse necessary information to understand the impact of our campaigns. If you don’t accept that we track you for this purpose, you will _still_ see adidas advertisements on other platforms at random. 

You can learn more about how our Advertising Partners help us achieve this purpose by visiting their sites:

**Google Personalised Advertising** : <https://support.google.com/adspolicy/answer/143465?hl=en>

**Google Advertising Policies** : https://support.google.com/adspolicy/answer/6020956

**Facebook Lookalike Audiences** : <https://www.facebook.com/business/help/164749007013531>

**Facebook Custom Audience Terms** : <https://www.facebook.com/legal/terms/customaudience>

**Use of Cookies/Tags/Pixels:** We may collect your personal details for this purpose by using technologies such as cookies, pixels and tags to collect your device information. More information is available in “ **XVIII.      COLLECTING YOUR DEVICE INFORMATION ON OUR WEBSITE USING COOKIES, PIXELS, TAGS, AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES**”.   
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Consent  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Identity information

Contact information (if available to adidas)

Location information

Size information (if available to adidas)

Purchase information (if available to adidas)

Behavioural and Profile information (if available to adidas)

Community information (if available to adidas)

Social Media information (if available to adidas)

Activity information (if available to adidas)

Device information

Preference information (if available to adidas)

Creators Club information (for Creators Club members only)  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

We retain it for as long as you do not withdraw your consent.  
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates 
  * Advertising Agency Partners
  * Social Media Platforms
  * Targeted Marketing Service Providers
  * IT Cloud Solution Providers

  13. CREATORS CLUB MEMBERSHIP ADMINISTRATION – WHERE APPLICABLE

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

_Please note this section only applies if you are joining adidas Creators Club to become a Creators Club member._

When you become an adidas Creators Club member, we use the information specified above to maintain and administer your membership as described in the Creators Club Terms and Conditions. 

In particular, your Personal Data is used for: 

a) calculating your club points to provide you rewards; 

b) providing you access to special offers and promotions; 

c) sending you invitations to exclusive events; 

d) allowing you access to limited edition products; 

e) providing you access to a premium Runtastic subscription when eligible; 

f) storing your shipping address and payment details to shorten check-out time online and in the app; 

f) storing your complete order history so you can access it at any time; and 

g) allowing you to track your order delivery from your account.

When you use your Creators Club membership ID, we receive the information to calculate reward points for you, such as when you purchase in participating adidas brand retail stores. Your data will be shared with Creators Club Partners who provide certain rewards according to Creators Club Terms and Conditions. 

You will receive email marketing messages from adidas as a Creators Club member. If you wish to unsubscribe from our marketing messages, please refer to “ **8.      What are your rights and how can you exercise them?**” section. 

You can also use your Creators Club membership in adidas apps. When you use adidas apps with your Creators Club membership, we use push notifications in the app to communicate information about your membership or promotional activities and offers. You can switch off push notifications at any time using “Settings” in your mobile devices. However, if you switch off push notifications, we may need to contact you via emails for important messages relating to your membership.  
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Performance of Contract  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Creators Club information

Size information (if available to adidas)

Purchase information (if available to adidas)

Behavioural and Profile information (if available to adidas)

Community information (if available to adidas)

Social Media information (if available to adidas)

Activity information (if available to adidas)

Device information (if available to adidas)

Preference information (if available to adidas)  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

Duration of contract and statutory limitation period. We need to keep the information in case of any legal disputes concerning the contract.   
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates 
  * Prospective Buyers and Investors
  * Business Consulting Service Providers
  * Data Analytics Solution Providers
  * Creators Club Partners

  14. PRIVATE EVENT REGISTRATION

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

When you sign up for an event we organise that have limited spots, we use the Personal Data you provide to reserve a spot for you. Your Personal Data will be used according to the Terms and Conditions associated with the event.  
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Performance of Contract  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Identity information

Contact information

Location information

Activity information: any information we may collect from you on the day of the event.

Creators Club information (for Creators Club members only)  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

Duration of the event and statutory limitation period in case of any disputes.   
  
**RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Controller organizing the event. 
  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates 
  * Event Partners (where applicable)
  * IT Cloud Solution Providers (where applicable)

  * XV. OPEN EVENT REGISTRATION

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

We often also organize events that are open to everyone. We use the Personal Data you provide to keep you inform of the events you are interested in.  
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Legitimate Interest  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Identity information

Contact information

Location information

Activity information: any information we may collect from you on the day of the event.

Creators Club information (for Creators Club members only)  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

For the duration of the event + 36 months if the data from a particular event is used for **BUSINESS OPERATIONAL ANALYTICS** purpose.   
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Controller organizing the event. 
  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates 
  * Event Partners (where applicable)
  * IT Cloud Solution Providers (where applicable)

  16. PRODUCT RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

We conduct analysis to research improve our products and services. This includes asking you questions in surveys, asking you for feedback, asking you to test our products and provide us with a review, asking other service providers to conduct market and product research for us, try new technologies in our product that might collect Personal Data to stay ahead of the competition. We retain this information based on our “legitimate interest”, so by participating in any product review or survey, you agree that this is our legitimate interest. Where you wish to object to this legitimate interest, we will anonymise your information, so it is no longer Personal Data.  
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Legitimate interest  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Identity information (only if required by the project)

Contact information (only if required by the project)

Location information (only if required by the project)

Size information

Purchase information (only if required by the project)

Behavioural and Profile information (only if required by the project)

Community information: this is the response you provided whichever format agreed at the time of the project.

Social Media information (only if required by the project)

Activity information (only if required by the project)

Device information (only if required by the project)

Correspondence (only if required by the project)

Preference information 

Creators Club information (for Creators Club members only)

Health information: **if a project requires you to also provide health information, we will explicitly ask for your consent.**  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

The duration of the project and statutory retention period stated to protect our IP rights.   
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates 
  * Prospective Buyers and Investors
  * Business Consulting Service Providers
  * Data Analytics Solution Providers
  * Manufacturing Providers
  * IT Cloud Solution Providers

  17. LEGAL OBLIGATION - COOPERATION WITH LAW ENFORCEMENT AND REGULATORY AUTHORITIES (INCLUDING COURTS)

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

When we are legally required to provide your Personal Data for national and public security reasons, crime prevention, investigation and prosecution, anti-money laundering, judicial proceedings, protection of other individuals’ rights and freedoms, and enforcement of civil claims, we will provide information as requested by the authorities or parties once we are satisfied that the request is mandated by law. We may not be able to notify you if it is against the law to do so.   
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Legal Obligation  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

All Categories of Personal Data as requested by the enforcement authority.  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

For as long as required by law.  
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates
  * Local and national government authorities, including tax authorities
  * Local and national law enforcement agencies
  * Local and national judiciary

  18. COLLECTING YOUR DEVICE INFORMATION ON OUR WEBSITE USING COOKIES, PIXELS, TAGS, AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES (“COOKIES NOTICE”)

---  
  
When you visit the adidas site, we store data collectors such as cookies, tags, pixels, tag containers, beacons, among others, in your browser to obtain certain information about your current browsing session. These technologies are often referred to as “ **Cookies** ” collectively by other websites. Cookies also enable our website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another. We use Cookies for different purposes, which also mean they have different legal bases. Please review the information below to understand how we use different types of Cookies to fulfil different purposes.  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

“ **REQUIRED** ” – site functionality and business operation. 

We use “ **Required Cookies** ” to operate our site. This includes storing a unique identifier to manage and identify you as a unique visitor to our site, to provide a consistent and accurate service to you. This includes making sure that we remember the products you have placed in your cart, or your language preferences. These Cookies are stored for the duration of your browsing session. Without these Cookies, you will not be able to view our site properly.  
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Legitimate Interest  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

“ **FUNCTIONAL** ” – website improvement and performance 

We use “ **Functional Cookies** ” to continuously improve our website performance. This includes using the data we collected from you to do the following: 

  * **Web analytics** —Based on your browsing behaviour, we will analyse the data to improve the functionality and design of our site. 
  * **Ad response rates** — Based on how you come to our site, we will measure our ad response rates by analysing our ad click-through rates to improve the effectiveness of advertising purchased on a site external to ours. 
  * **Affiliate tracking** — We need to let our affiliate marketing partners, or service providers have certain information if you came to our site, and purchased products, through a visit to theirs. This is required as we may need to provide them a fee for such services. For this purpose, we will share information about your visit, including the products you have purchased. 
  * **Error management** — We measure errors presented on a website, to make sure we fix bugs or any issues promptly. 
  * **Testing designs** — We need to use A/B testing or multivariate testing, to ensure a consistent look and feel is maintained for the user of the site in the current and subsequent sessions.

**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Legitimate Interest  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

“ **MARKETING** ”

We use “ **Marketing Cookies** ” provided by our advertising partners to make sure our advertising messages are shown to you at the right time and the right place. These Cookies are persistent but time-limited cookies. These Cookies contain a unique key to distinguish individual users’ browsing habits. We also use these Cookies to limit the number of times a user sees a particular ad on a website and to measure the effectiveness of a particular campaign. The identifier stored by these Cookies are provided by our partners. We cannot use the same identifier in our own systems. We also use these cookies to serve ads that are relevant to your immediate geo-location, for example to provide you with the nearest store where the product you are browsing may be available.   
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Consent  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Device information

Location information

Behavioural and Profile information: this is collected through observing your browsing behaviour

Preference information (if available to adidas)  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

The cookies, pixels, tags, and other similar technologies used to collect your device information and browsing behaviour information are stored in your browser for the session or for as long as you do not clear your browser cookie setting. 

The data we obtained through the cookies related to other purposes will be stored for the duration of that purpose.  
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates
  * Site Administration Support Providers
  * Business Consulting Service Providers
  * Data Analytics Solution Providers
  * Advertising Agency Partners
  * Social Media Platforms
  * Targeted Marketing Service Providers

| 

You can change your browser settings to delete or prevent certain cookies from being stored on your computer or mobile device without your explicit consent. The ‘help’ section in your browser should provide information on how to manage your cookie settings. 

Find out how this works for your browser here:

Internet Explorer: <https://support.microsoft.com/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies>

Mozilla Firefox: <http://support.mozilla.com/en-US/kb/Cookies>

Google Chrome: [http://www.google.com/support/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647](http://www.google.com/support/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647)

Safari: <http://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042>

Opera: <http://www.opera.com/browser/tutorials/security/privacy/>

Adobe (flash cookies): <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/policies/flash-player.html>

Google Chrome App: [https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416?co=GENIE.Platform%3DAndroid&hl=en](https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416?co=GENIE.Platform%3DAndroid&hl=en)

These websites will also help you understand more about how Cookie-based advertising works and how you can manage your Cookie Settings:

<http://www.aboutads.info/choices>

<http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>

Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page: <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1>

You can learn more about the laws governing the use of “Cookies” here: <http://ec.europa.eu/ipg/basics/legal/cookies/index_en.htm>  
  
  19. USER-GENERATED CONTENT (UGC) ACQUISITION FROM SOCIAL MEDIA

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

We invite you to provide your images to us via social media platforms by following specific instructions such as “#yesadidas”. We will be using the images you provide for our campaign communications. We will obtain rights to your image through a licence agreement in the form of our terms and conditions. By submitting your images via social media platforms to us, you will agree for us to use your images as described in the licence agreement.  
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Performance of Contract  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Identity information: your social media handler

Community information: images, videos, comments, sound recordings and other files provided through the social media platform promoting adidas

Social Media information  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

Duration of licence agreement and statutory limitation period in case of any disputes.   
  
**RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates 
  * Event Partners (where applicable)
  * UGC Support Partners
  * Advertising Agency Partners
  * Social Media Platforms
  * IT Cloud Solution Providers (where applicable)

  * XX. PUSH NOTIFICATIONS (IN-APP COMMUNICATION)

---  
  
**PROCESSING**

| 

When you use the adidas app, we use push notifications in this app to communicate with you concerning the purposes stated in this Notice. This includes information that relates to purposes based on the Performance of Contract (such as your purchase). You can switch off push notifications at any time using “Settings” in your mobile devices. However, if you switch off push notifications, we may need to contact you via emails for important messages relating to your purchase.   
  
**LEGAL BASIS**

| 

Legitimate Interest  
  
**CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA**

| 

Device information  
  
**RETENTION PERIOD**

| 

For as long as you use the app and not switched Push Notification off.  
  
**CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS**

| 

  * adidas Data Controllers
  * adidas AG Subsidiaries and Affiliates

  6. What does adidas do when we transfer your Personal Data outside of the EU/EEA?

Depending on the Personal Data processing activity, your Personal Data is shared with different “Categories of Recipients”. Where the recipient is located outside the EU/EEA, we have implemented necessary measures such as singing the EU Standard Contractual Clauses approved by the EU Commission or selecting vendors that certify and comply with the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework. 

  7. How do we secure your Personal Data?

We implement appropriate technical and organisational measures to address the risks corresponding to our use of your Personal Data, including loss, alteration, or unauthorised access to your Personal Data, and empowering you to exercise your rights. We require our service providers to do the same through contractual agreements. However, you should be aware that any transmission of your Personal Data through the internet is at your own risk. We can only protect your Personal Data when we have it.

  8. What are your rights and how can you exercise them?

Under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws in the EU/EEA countries, you have the rights listed and explained below. We need to confirm your identity before we can handle your requests. When we refuse your request for legal reasons, we will tell you why. 

**For all enquiries concerning your privacy and personal data, please contact us under the “ASK CUSTOMER SERVICE” section via**[ **HELP**](https://www.adidas.ie/help) **.**

_Please consult your local supervisory authority about your rights under the GDPR and to understand what these rights mean._

**YOUR RIGHT S**

|   
---|---  
  
  1. **Get a copy of your Personal Data**

You have the right to obtain a copy of your Personal Data, if it does not have negative effect on other people.  
  
  2. **Access to information about your Personal Data**

You have the right to know whether or not we use your Personal Data, as well as the following information: a) why we have your Personal Data; b) what categories of data we have; c)  what we do with your Personal Data; d) who has access to your Personal Data (and where they are); e) where your Personal Data might be transferred to; f) how long we are keeping your Personal Data; g) if you didn’t provide your Personal Data directly to us, how did we get them; h) your rights under applicable laws and the possibility to restrict processing; and i) if we use your Personal Data for any automated decision-making; and j) in some cases, you have the right to know how our automated decision-making works, if the decision significantly affects you.  
  
  3. **Make sure your Personal Data are correct**

You have the right to make sure we are using the accurate details about you.  
  
  4. **Delete your Personal Data**

You have the right to ask us to delete your Personal Data if: a) we no longer need it for a specific purpose, for example, a contract or a legal requirement; or b) you withdraw the consent you provided if we asked for your consent when we collected your Personal Data; or c) if you object to our use of your Personal Data based on legitimate interests we have identified, including direct marketing activities, unless we can demonstrate the compelling need of the legitimate interests.  
  
  5. **Restrict how we use your Personal Data**

You have the right to stop us from doing certain things to your Personal Data when: a) you don’t think we are using the right Personal Data; b) you don't want us to delete your Personal Data, but you also don't think we are complying with the law; c) you want to make a legal complaint against us, but we want to delete the data; or d) you challenge our explanation of our use based on a "legitimate interest". When you successfully restrict how we use your Personal Data, we will only use your Personal Data with your consent, or unless it is required by law.  
  
  6. **Obtain a portable file so you can share it with another company**

You have the right to obtain a portable file that contains the Personal Data you provided to us where the legal basis is either consent or the performance of contract. The file will provide you with the Personal Data you actively and knowingly provided to us, including data passively obtained by us when you use our service or products.   
  
  7. **Withdraw your consent**

When we use your Personal Data based on your consent, you have the right to change your mind and withdraw your consent at any time.   
  
  8. **Object when we process your Personal Data based on “Legitimate Interest”**

When we process your Personal Data based on “Legitimate Interest” as specified in this Privacy Notice, you may have the right to disagree and stop us from processing your Personal Data for this purpose. We may have compelling reasons, though, to continue processing your Personal Data even in the light of your objection. In such cases we will provide you with our rationale. We will respect and implement your objection in any case where it is related to direct marketing purposes.  
  
  9. **Challenge the decision generated by our automated decision-making process**

When we use automated decision-making tools or processes that lead to an outcome which produces a legal effect (such as Payment Fraud Detection), you have the right to understand the logic involved, the significance and possible consequences of this process. You also have the right to request human intervention, especially when this is used to conclude a contract with us. You can challenge our decision by expressing your opinion.   
  
  10. **File a complaint with your local data protection supervisory authority**

If you are not happy with how we have handled your Personal Data, or how we have responded to your rights provided here, you have the right to make a complaint against us with your local data protection supervisory authority.   
  
  9. Questions, Complaints, and Support – who and how you can get in touch with them?

adidas Customer Service  
  
---  
  
**ASK CUSTOMER SERVICE:** [**https://www.adidas.ie/help**](https://www.adidas.ie/help)  
  
adidas Privacy Team and the Data Protection Officer  

**Global Privacy | Data Protection Officer**

**adidas AG**

Adi-Dassler-Strasse 1

91074 Herzogenaurach

Germany  
  
Data Protection Supervisory Authorities

|   
  
**adidas Lead Supervisory Authority**

Bayerisches Landesamt für Datenschutzaufsicht (BayLDA)

+49 (0) 981 53 1300

Promenade 27 

91522 Ansbach

Germany

<https://www.lda.bayern.de/de/kontakt.html>

| 

**Your Local EU/EEA Supervisory Authority**

**Please find the details to your local Data Protection Supervisory Authority here:**

<https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en>  
  
  10. Updates and Notification of Updates

We review and update the Privacy Notice periodically to reflect any changes resulting from our day-to-day business operations. You can always check the date of the Privacy Notice to find out when we last made any changes. We will notify you when we make significant changes that you must be aware of. 

  11. adidas Data Recipients

You can find a list of adidas Data Recipients who processes your personal data under adidas Data Controllers’ instructions below. The list is subject to change as necessary. 

**COMPANY**

| 

**SERVICE**  
  
---|---  
  
adidas International Marketing B.V.

| 

Webshop operations & Marketing Services  
  
Demandware Inc.| USA

| 

Website Hosting  
  
Adyen | Netherlands

| 

Payment Processes  
  
InfoSys Technologies Ltd. | India, EPAM | Belarus

| 

Website Development  
  
Adobe Analytics | Ireland, Google Analytics | USA

| 

Web Analytics  
  
Sprinklr | USA, Olapic Inc. | USA

| 

Social Media Analytics  
  
Flurry | USA, Apps Flyer | Israel

| 

Mobile App Analytics  
  
Medallia Inc. | USA, Qualtrics LLC | USA

| 

Net Promoter Score  
  
act.3 | Germany, cip Trademarketing GmbH | Germany

| 

Event Management  
  
Neolane Ltd. | France

| 

Marketing  
  
Batterii LLC | USA

| 

Consumer Insights  
  
TBWA Worldwide Inc. | USA, Media Monk Netherlands, IRIS | Australia

| 

CRM Agencies  
  
Olapic, Inc. | USA

| 

UGC Support Partners  
  
adidas affiliates | globally

| 

Consumer Relationship Management  
  
Teleperformance | Germany

| 

Customer Service  
  
DHL | Germany

| 

Product Delivery  
  
Feedzai | Germany

| 

Fraud Prevention  
  
PayPal | USA

| 

Payment Service  
  
Apple Pay, Google Pay | USA

| 

Mobile Payment  
  
Facebook (WhatsApp, Instagram) | USA

| 

Social Media Interaction  
  
Twitter | USA

| 

Social Media Interaction  
  
Google | USA

| 

Social Media Interaction  
  
Runtastic | Austria

| 

Health and Fitness Community  
  
Google Analytics | USA

| 

Analytics  
  
Adobe Analytics | USA

| 

Analytics  
  
Anatwine Limited | UK

| 

Consumer Experience  
  
MediaCom | UK

| 

Advertising Partner  
  
Salesforce

| 

CRM Software | Data Analytics  
  
Wunderman

| 

Email Marketing Services  
  
_Where your personal data may be used by non-adidas Data Controllers via adidas platforms, applications or elsewhere for their own purposes, please consult the privacy notice of the non-adidas Data Controller for more information about how they handle your personal data._
